I'm going out to South Park gonna have myself a time
Friendly faces everywhere humble folks without temptation
I'm goin out to south park gonna leave my woes behind
Ample parking day or night people spouting howdy neighbor
I'm heading out to south park to see if i cant unwind
I like girls with big fat titties really big fat titties
So come on out to south park and meet some friends of mine
South.Park.S11E07.Night.of.the.Living.Homeless
好了 这一次
ALRIGHT, THIS TIME
就有我和Kenny来对抗 你们这两个小屁眼吧
IT'S ME AND KENNY VERSUS YOU TWO ASSHOLES
谁怕谁呀
FINE
噢 天啊! 篮球场怎么这么多流浪汉呀?!
OH, DUDE! WHAT'S WITH ALL THE HOMELESS PEOPLE?!
先生 麻烦你稍微挪下位置好吗?
SIR? COULD YOU MOVE A LITTLE PLEASE?
赏点零钱好吗?
SPARE SOME CHANGE?
噢! 篮球场现在和Kenny他们家一样臭!
OH, DUDE HE SMELLS LIKE KENNY'S HOUSE!
快滚!!!
GET OUTTA HERE!!!
伙计们 这不大好吧
YOU GUYS, THAT'S NOT COOL
这些人没有其他地方可去了
THESE PEOPLE HAVE NOWHERE TO GO
他们没有食物和住所
THEY DON'T HAVE FOOD OR SHELTER
我们得做些什么
WE HAVE TO DO SOMETHING
那好吧 可我们应该怎么做呢?
WELL, DUDE WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED TO DO?
没错 我们该怎么做呢?
YEAH, WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED TO DO?
我觉得Kyle说的没错 伙计们 我们得有所行动!
NO, KYLE'S RIGHT, YOU GUYS WE SHOULD DO SOMETHING
真的?
REALLY?
没错!
YEAH
我知道你在想什么 Kyle
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE THINKING, KYLE
我站在你这边!
AND I'M WITH YOU
我非常清楚我们应该做什么
I KNOW EXACTLY WHAT WE SHOULD DO
大家都过来啊 一起见证下
GATHER ROUND AND WITNESS THE GLORY
Eric Cartman惊世骇俗的 "滑板飞跃流浪汉"特技吧
AS ERIC CARTMAN ATTEMPTS TO JUMP HIS SKATEBOARD OVER THE HOMELESS!
多谢捧场!
THANK YOU!
场地布置好了吗?
THE RAMP READY?
全部都弄好了
YEAH, IT'S ALL SET
他不会成功的...
HE WON'T MAKE IT
我操!
EXCUSE ME!
这根本就不是我要做的事!
THIS ISN'T EXACTLY WHAT I HAD IN MIND!
好啦 我要冲刺啦!
ALRIGHT -- HERE WE GO!
Jimmy?
JIMMY?
OOF!
UGH
YES!!!!
我成功了!
I DID IT!!!
我成功飞跃流浪汉了!!
I JUMPED OVER THE HOMELESS!!
太棒了!!!
YES!!!
这可真是个好主意啊 Kyle
THAT WAS A SWEET IDEA, KYLE
我日 这和我没有任何关系!!
GOD DAMMIT, THAT WASN'T MY IDEA!!
好啦 公民们 我们一定得想个办法才行
ALRIGHT PEOPLE, WE NEED TO COME UP WITH ANSWERS
我们现在全镇都被流浪汉赛满了
THERE ARE HOMELESS SPROUTING UP ALL OVER TOWN
我们应该怎么处理这件事呢?
WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED TO DO?
嗯 我倒是有一个主意
WELL, I SORT OF HAD AN IDEA
请说吧  Valmer先生
PLEASE, MR. VALMER
我们可以给他们一些式样美观的睡袋 再帮他们化点小妆
WE COULD GIVE THE HOMELESS ALL DESIGNER SLEEPING BAGS AND MAKE-OVERS
这也算是为构建和谐社会 尽了自己的一份力吧
AT LEAST THAT WAY THEY'D BE PLEASANT TO LOOK AT
- 这主意可真不错 - 我觉得挺好的
- OH, THAT'S GOOD - I LIKE THAT
- 好办法 - 太棒了
- GOOD IDEA - I LIKE IT
嗯 我倒有个另外的想法
WELL, I WAS THINKING --
我们可以把他们改造成轮胎什么的
WE COULD TURN THE HOMELESS INTO TIRES
这样的话我们就不用担心轮胎磨损的问题了
SO THAT WE'D STILL HAVE HOMELESS BUT WE COULD USE THEM ON OUR CARS
- 这办法也不错! - 真屌啊 Randy
- OOH, THAT'S GOOD - NICE ONE, RANDY
- 我挺喜欢这办法的 - 有点像废物循环利用
- I LIKE IT - THAT'S LIKE RECYCLING
我实在是受够!
ALRIGHT, ENOUGH
这次会议也太失败了 你们难道没有同情心吗?
I FIND THIS WHOLE CONVERSATION TO BE EXTREMELY OFFENSIVE
流浪汉又不是外星怪物
THE HOMELESS AREN'T MONSTERS
他们也是人呀
THEY ARE PEOPLE
和我们一样的人
LIKE YOU AND ME
你是说他们可以...
YOU MEAN THEY'VE ADAPTED?
..吸纳我们的DNA?
COPIED OUR DNA?
各位
EXCUSE ME
我是镇上流浪汉研究问题的最高权威
I AM THE TOP RESEARCHER OF HOMELESS STUDIES FOR PARK COUNTY
虽然我不知道流浪汉们出现的原因
I DON'T KNOW WHY MORE HOMELESS PEOPLE ARE SHOWING UP IN TOWN
但我知道一件事 我们必须得加倍小心
BUT I DO KNOW THAT WE MUST BE EXTREMELY CAREFUL
如果我们给了他们什么东西的话-
IF WE GIVE THEM ANYTHING --
他们的数量会加倍增加的
THERE COULD BE MORE
嗨
HI
我正在为买XBOX的游戏暂钱呢 可是
I'VE, UH -- I'VE BEEN SAVING UP FOR A NEW XBOX GAME, BUT --
可是我觉得你比我更需要这笔钱
BUT I THINK YOU COULD USE THE MONEY A LOT MORE THAN I COULD
我希望你能够收下这20美元
LISTEN, I WANT YOU TO TAKE THIS
IT'S $20
再给点好吗?
GOT ANY MORE?
我没钱啦.. 可我觉得20美元够多了呀...
NO, THAT'S -- I THOUGHT THAT WAS A LOT
赏点零钱好吗?
SPARE ANY CHANGE?
拜拜...
YOU'RE WELCOME
天啊..
OH, CRAP
兄弟 你家门口怎么聚集了这么多流浪汉啊?
DUDE, WHAT ARE ALL THESE HOMELESS PEOPLE DOING IN FRONT OF YOUR HOUSE?
我不知道!
I DON'T KNOW!
我家门扣也有好一堆呢!
THERE'S A BUNCH OUTSIDE OF MY HOUSE, TOO!
赏点零钱好吗 先生?
SPARE ANY CHANGE, SIR?
滚远点!
NO! GOD -
真奇怪耶
I DON'T GET IT
我老爸说如果他们的不到零钱的话 就会自动转移的
MY DAD SAID AS LONG AS NOBODY GAVE THEM MONEY THEY'D MOVE ON
真的?
HE DID?
我操 肯定是出什么事了
WELL, THIS IS BULLCRAP
肯定有人施舍给他们钱了吧
SOMEBODY HAS TO BE RESPONSIBLE
嗯 我..我昨天晚上 给了个流浪汉20美圆
WELL, I -- KIND OF GAVE A HOMELESS GUY TWENTY DOLLARS LAST NIGHT
什么?!
YOU WHAT?!
可是 这不是他们聚集在这的原因吧?
COME ON, THAT CAN'T BE WHY THEY'RE ALL HERE
肯定有其他的什么原因的!
THERE HAS TO BE ANOTHER REASON!
Kyle 你到底在想什么呀?!
KYLE, WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?!
我根本就飞越不了这么多的流浪汉呢!
YEAH, I CAN'T POSSIBLY JUMP THIS MANY HOMELESS PEOPLE!
我不会冒险的
I WON'T RISK IT
我可以飞过两个 三个也许勉强能试试..
I COULD JUMP TWO HOMELESS PEOPLE MAYBE THREE
可是叫我飞跃这么流浪汉 是在拿我的生命开玩笑啊 Kyle!
BUT ASKING ME TO JUMP THIS MANY IS ASKING ME TO RISK MY LIFE, KYLE!
我又没叫你去跳 傻逼!
I DON'T WANT YOU TO JUMP THEM, RETARD!
赏点零钱好吗?
SPARE SOME CHANGE?
哦 对不起 我没有零钱了
NO, SORRY, I DON'T HAVE ANY CHANGE
有零钱吗?
GOT ANY CHANGE?
没了噢 不好意思
NO, SORRY
大爷 赏点零钱好吗?
CAN YOU SPARE SOME CHANGE?
零...零..钱?
CHAAAANGE?
啊 我没有零钱啊!
AGH -- I DON'T HAVE ANY CHANGE!
赏点好吗?
CHANGE?
不要!
NO!
赏点好吗!!
CHANGE!!
赏点零钱好吗?
SPARE SOME CHANGE?
离我远点 我没有零钱!
LEAVE ME ALONE I DON'T HAVE ANY CHANGE
好吧 愿上帝保佑你 先生
ALRIGHT, GOD BLESS YOU, SIR
噢 我怎么会有犯罪感...
OH, NOW I FEEL BAD
给你..
HERE! AH! AAAAAH...
赏点好吗?!
CHANNNGE?!!
刚才那是我仅有的零钱了呀
THAT WAS REALLY ALL THE CHANGE I HAD
赏点零钱好吗?
SPARE SOME CHANGE?
我刚刚才给过你了呀!
I JUST GAVE YOU CHANGE!
AHGGHHG!!!
零钱!
CHANGE!
赏点零钱好吗??
SPARE SOME CHANGE??
AAAAAAH...
我真的没有零钱了!
I DON'T HAVE ANY MORE CHANGE!
CHANNGE
GOT ANY CHANGE?!?!
GOD BLESS
NOO!!!!
我真的没有零钱了!
I DON'T HAVE ANY CHANGE!!!
我真的没有零钱了!...
I DON'T HAVE ANY CHANGE...
好啦 就这么定了吧
OKAY, THAT'LL BE GREAT
但是要确定我们能不能找到足够多的椅子 到场人数会很多咧
LET'S ALSO MAKE SURE WE HAVE ENOUGH CHAIRS IN THE COMMUNITY CENTER FOR EVERYONE TO ATTEND
AAHGHGHHGGHH!!!
AHGHGHGGHH!!!
离我远点!!
STAY AWAY!!
离我远点!
STAY AWAY!!!!!!
Randy!?!
RANDY!?!
Randy 发生什么事了?!?!
RANDY, WHAT HAPPENED?!?!
我真的没有零钱呀!!
I DON'T HAVE ANY CHANGE!!!
现在是Chris Swollenballs为你献上的 新闻5台特别报道
THIS IS A NEWS 5 SPECIAL BULLETIN WITH CHRIS SWOLLENBALLS
流浪汉充斥了南方公园的每一个角落
SOUTH PARK HAS BECOME OVERRUN WITH THE HOMELESS
基本上所有的公众场合 ...都塞满了流浪汉
NEARLY EVERY SQUARE INCH OF PUBLIC PROPERTY IS NOW RIDDLED WITH HOMELESS
出镇的路基本上都被流浪汉封死了
SHUTTING DOWN ROADWAYS AND MAKING GETTING AROUND IMPOSSIBLE
许多人被困在了镇上
MANY PEOPLE ARE TRAPPED THROUGHOUT THE TOWN
HELLLPP!!!
HELP US!!!! HELP ME!!!!!!
伙计 那是我爸爸他们呀!
DUDE! IT'S OUR DADS!
噢 天啊
OH, MY GOD
在这个非常时期 所有居民都应做好守在家里
IN THE MEANTIME, SOUTH PARK CITIZENS ARE BEING ADVISED TO STAY INDOORS
及保护好零钱的准备
AND PROTECT THEIR CHANGE
赏点零钱好吗?
SPARE SOME CHANGE?
什么鸟.. 你是怎么混进来的?
WHAT THE -- YOU CAN'T BE IN HERE
给点零钱好吗 先生?
YOU GOT ANY CHANGE, SIR?
才不 我没有零钱!
NO, I DON'T HAVE ANY CHANGE!
你是怎么进来的呀...?!
HOW'D HE GET IN HERE?!
CHAAAAANGE?
NO! PLEASE!
我真的没有零钱呀E!!
I DON'T HAVE ANY CHANGE!!
我发誓 我真的没呀!
HONEST, I DON'T!
我真的没有...
I DON'T HAVE ANY--
DOOOOOOOOOOOO
看看你都做了什么 Kyle?
YOU SEE WHAT YOU DID, KYLE?
好啦 快去把我们的傻逼爸爸们救出来吧
COME ON, WE HAVE TO TRY AND HELP OUR STUPID PARENTS
到处都是流浪汉啊!
THEY'RE EVERYWHERE!
你们在干什么呀?
WHAT ARE YOU BOYS DOING?
快进来!
GET IN!
有零钱吗 先生?
GOT ANY CHANGE, SIR?
好啦 快走啊!
COME ON, LET'S GO!
你们在户外干什么卵呀?
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING OUTSIDE?
我老爸他们被困在南方中心上了..
MY PARENTS ARE STUCK ON TOP OF A BUILDING IN TOWN
我们现在进不去呀
YOU AREN'T GETTING INTO TOWN
路都被这些流浪汉堵死了
IT'S COMPLETELY OVERRUN WITH THESE THINGS
不要啊!
NO!
不要擦我的窗户啊
NO, I DON'T NEED MY WIND SHIELD CLEANED
快停下!
STOP IT!
听好 我们唯一的希望就是找到 那个流浪汉问题首席权威
LOOK, OUR ONLY HOPE IS TO TALK TO THE HOMELESS RESEARCHER ON ??? STREET
这种时候只有他才知道怎么做了
HE UNDERSTANDS WHAT IS GOING ON BETTER THAN ANYBODY
你们和我在一起很安全
JUST STICK WITH ME, KIDS
AGGGH!
这一切还真扯啊...
HOLY - DUDE
这儿!
OVER HERE
快下来吧 Kyle
JUMP DOWN, KYLE
噢 这地方闻起来还真像Kenny他们家呀
OH, GOD, IT REALLY SMELLS LIKE KENNY'S HOUSE DOWN HERE
???
别生气 Kenny 放轻松 伙计们!
WHOA, KENNY, RELAX, DUDE!
我们得齐心协力才行
WE NEED TO WORK TOGETHER
加油 我们必须找到那个权威
COME ON, WE GOT TO GET TO THAT SCIENTIST'S HOUSE
CHANGE!
CHANGE...
根本就没有救援人员出现啊
NO SIGN OF ANYBODY ELSE
我受够了
THAT'S IT
我要杀出重围去求救!
I'M GOING TO MAKE A BREAK FOR IT
别犯傻了 Gerald!
DON'T BE CRAZY, GERALD!
你是不可能穿越这么多流浪汉的!
YOU WILL NEVER GET THROUGH ALL THOSE HOMELESS PEOPLE!
而且就算你穿过了 那又怎么样呢?
AND EVEN IF YOU DID, WHAT THEN?
你也根本没办法开车
YOU CAN'T DRIVE ANYWHERE
可是如果我能成功穿越的话 我也许能搭得到公车呀???
IF I WITH MAKE IT THROUGH THEM MAYBE I CAN CATCH THE BUS TO FIRE ???
我必须得试试
I HAVE TO TRY
你不会成功的 Gerald!
YOU WON'T MAKE IT THROUGH, GERALD!
- CHANGE? - SPARE SOME CHANGE?
AHHHH!
CHANGE, SIR?
GOT SOME CHANGE? CHANGE
我没有零钱!
DON'T HAVE ANY CHANGE!
CHANGE?
CHANGE, SIR?
我没有零钱!
DON'T HAVE ANY CHANGE!
CHANGE?
操 好吧 你要零钱是不
DAMMIT! ALL RIGHT YOU WANT CHANGE
这里!
HERE!
好啦 再给点吧
ALL RIGHT A LITTLE BIT
都拿去吧
THERE YOU GO TAKE THE CHANGE
CHANGE?
等等 我没有零钱搭公车了..
WAIT, I DON'T HAVE ANY CHANGE LEFT FOR THE BUS
不好意思 我可以要一些零钱回来吗 谢谢?
HOLD ON, CAN I JUST GET BACK SOME OF THAT CHANGE, PLEASE?
有零钱吗 先生?
CHANGE, SIR?
我可不可以拿回点零钱坐公车啊? 求求你了
CAN I HAVE JUST A LITTLE CHANGE FOR THE BUS, PLEASE
我就要一点 -- 能给些零钱吗?
I NEED A LITTLE -- ANYBODY HAVE SOME CHANGE?
有零钱吗?
CHANGE?
给点零钱好吗?
GOT ANY CHANGE?
有零钱吗?
CHANGE?
发生什么事了?
WHAT HAPPENED?
他..被它们同化了...
HE HAS BECOME ONE OF THEM
CHANGE CHANGE...
CHANGE CHANGE
滚远点 我可没有零钱
GO AWAY I DON'T HAVE ANY CHANGE
你就是那个流浪汉研究权威吗?
ARE YOU THE HEAD OF HOMELESS STUDIES?
没错
YES
你们是..?
WHO ARE YOU?
现在这一切也许是我们造成的
WE THINK THIS MAY BE OUR FRIEND'S FAULT
他昨天给了个流浪汉20美元
HE GAVE ONE OF THE HOMELESS TWENTY DOLLARS YESTERDAY
哦 天啊
OH, MY GOD
快进来!
GET IN HERE!
到底发生什么事了?
TELL ME WHAT'S GOING ON
镇中央有一群人被流浪汉给困住了..
THERE'S A BUNCH OF PEOPLE TRAPPED IN THE MIDDLE OF TOWN SURROUNDED BY HOMELESS PEOPLE
我们想把他们救出来
WE CAN'T GET TO THEM
好啦 好啦!
ALRIGHT, ALRIGHT!
听好 虽然我真的不想冒险
LOOK, I DIDN'T WANT TO RISK IT
但我会以大局为重的
BUT I THINK I KNOW WHAT TO DO
我会试着飞跃这些流浪汉
I'LL TRY TO JUMP ALL THOSE HOMELESS
并救出那些被围困的人..
AND GET TO THE PEOPLE ON THAT ROOF
飞跃他们...
JUMP THEM
我是飞跃流浪汉职业选手
I JUMP THE HOMELESS PROFESSIONALLY
只要给我一个滑板 我就能飞跃整个地球
IF YOU CAN GIVE ME SKATEBOARD I TRY TO ??? SAVE THOES PEOPLE
给我闭嘴 Cartman!
OH, SHUT UP, CARTMAN!
你只不过飞越了一个流浪汉而已!
ALL YOU DID WAS JUMP OVER ONE HOMELESS GUY!
飞跃三十到四十个 对我来说也不是不可能的事
I EASILY COULD HAVE CLEARED ANOTHER THIRTY OR FORTY
你飞跃一个的时候都很勉强了 肥猪!
YOU BARELY MADE IT OVER ONE, FAT ASS!
Kyle 够了!
KYLE, ENOUGH!
Cartman能够飞越多少个流浪汉 根本就不是问题的重点
CARTMAN JUMPING MORE HOMELESS PEOPLE ISN'T GOING TO SOLVE ANYTHING RIGHT NOW
我操!
GOD!  DAMMIT! -
又不是我让他们跳的
I DON'T WANT HIM TO JUMP OVER MORE
孩子们
BOYS, BOYS
我想你们还不是太了解流浪汉这个物种吧?
I DON'T THINK YOU UNDERSTAND HOW THE HOMELESS FUNCTION
你们和我一起去楼下看看好了
PERHAPS YOU SHOULD COME DOWNTARES
我的实验室在那
TO MY LABORATORY
有零钱吗? 赏点零钱吧..
CHANGE? GOT SOME CHANGE?
赏点吧 先生
CHANGE, SIR?
我们没有零钱!
WE DON'T HAVE ANY CHANGE!
闪远点!
GO AWAY!
有消息吗 Steven
ANYTHING, STEVEN
没呢
NO
所有电话都是"无人接听"
ALL THE PHONE LINES ARE COMPLETELY DOWN
哈罗?
HELLO?
我是图书馆的Steve Garret呀
IT'S STEVE GARRETT FROM THE LIBRARY
快让我们进来吧
PLEASE, LET US IN
你还是去别的地方吧 Steve
FIND ANOTHER PLACE TO HIDE, STEVE!
我这还有其他人哪
I HAVE OTHERS WITH ME
我们没地方可躲了
WITH NO WHERE ELSE TO GO
有名妇女还怀孕了呢
ONE WOMAN HERE IS PREGNANT
不能就这样把他们关在外面吧
CAN'T JUST LEAVE THEM OUT THERE
让我们进来吧...
LET US IN
看在上帝他老人家的面子上
FOR GOD SAKES THEY'RE COMING
没有啊 我都说过我们没有零钱了...
NO, I'M SORRY WE DON'T HAVE ANY CHANGE
你得让他们进来呀 Randy
YOU HAVE TO LET THEM IN, RANDY
可如果一下子来那么多人 我们的食物就不够分了啊
THERE ISN'T ENOUGH FOOD FOR MORE PEOPLE UP HERE
噢 天啊 这还有个流浪汉是越战老兵
OH, GOD, ONE OF THEM IS A WAR VETERAN
我们没办法不给他些零钱....
WE ARE GOING TO HAVE TO GIVE HIM SOME CHANGE
这一切不是真的...
THIS ISN'T HAPPENING
好吧 好吧 我受够了
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT FINE
能给点零钱吗 先生?
COULD YOU SPARE SOME CHANGE, SIR
AHHHHH!
我曾经解剖过好几个流浪汉 来分析它们身体的构造
I HAVE DISSECTED SEVERAL HOMELESS TO SEE WHAT MAKES THEM TICK
它们的骨骼构造和我们似乎没有多大区别
THEIR ANATOMY IS SHOCKINGLY SIMILAR TO OURS
看到了吗 所有东西都一样..
SEE? EVERYTHING IS THERE
心脏 肺 肾..
HEART, LUNG, KIDNEYS
它们简直就和我们是同一个物种
THEY ARE ALMOST IDENTICAL TO US IN EVERY WAY
除了一点...
EXCEPT FOR ONE
流浪汉只需要零钱..就可以生存
THE HOMELESS CAN SURVIVE SOLELY ON CHANGE
赏点吧?
CHANGE?
他们可以从零钱中汲取营养
THEY FEED ON OUR CHANGE
从而获得生存的动力..
THEY NEED IT IN ORDER TO KEEP THEM MOVING
能不能给点零钱呀?
IS THAT SOME SPARE CHANGE?
这就是说 我们的零钱对它们来说不过是食物罢了
SOMEHOW, THEY ARE ABLE TO TAKE OUR CHANGE AND TURN IT INTO NOURISHMENT ???
您老就赏点吧 大爷
CAN I HAVE SOME OF THAT CHANGE, SIR
现在看好了哦
BUT NOW, WATCH
赏点零钱好吗?
SPARE SOME CHANGE?
它一瞬间就全然忘记了我刚刚給过它零钱的事
IT HAS ALREADY COMPLETELY FOREGOTTEN THAT I HAVE GIVE THEN CHANGE
它只是不停地索要零钱而已
IT JUST WANTS MORE CHANGE
看看这个吧
LOOK OVER HERE
它已经三天没有收到零钱了..
THIS ONE HAS KEPT DEPRIVED OF CHANGE FOR OVER THREE DAYS
零..钱..
CHANGE
看到了吧? 它离死不远了
- WHAT IS IT DOING? - IT'S DYING
哇 真屌
COOL
我听说不久前常青树镇 也爆发了一次严重的流浪汉施虐
I HAVE LEARNED THAT THE NEARBY CITY OF EVERGREEN HAD A HOMELESS PROBLEM JUST BEFORE WE DID
但是他们成功解决了这个难题
AND THEY WERE ABLE TO STOP IT
不好意思
EXCUSE ME
前门是开着的
THE FRONT DOOR WAS OPEN
我能借些零钱吗?
CAN I BORROW SOME CHANGE?
赏点吧... 上帝会保佑你的灵魂的
CHANGE... GOD BLESS YOU, JUST CHANGE
噢 天哪 他们正不断的涌进来...
OH, MY GOD THEY'RE COMING IN
孩子们 快离开这儿
QUICK, KIDS GET OUT OF HERE
拯救这个城市
YOU CAN FIT
那你怎么办?
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
快去常青树镇请教一下 解决流浪汉施虐的方法
GET TO EVERGREEN AND FIND OUT HOW THEY GOT RID OF THE HOMELESS
别为我担心
I'LL BE ALRIGHT
别猥亵我的屁股...Kenny
??? STOP PUSHING
哈罗 不好意思 我真的需要搭公车的零钱
HELLO, SORRY, I JUST REALLY NEED CHANGE FOR THE BUS
CHANGE
SPARE SOME CHANGE CHANGE
我操! 我是真的急需零钱呀
STOP IT! I REALLY DO NEED CHANGE
大家都一样嘛...
ME, TOO, CHANGE?
CHANGE?
好罗 给点零钱好吗?
HELLO, DO YOU HAVE ANY CHANGE?
CHANGE
永别了 残酷滴世界...
SORRY TO TAKE THE EASY WAY OUT
OW!
OH
OH!
OH.
AHHH.
GOD!
OH, OH, OH, OH, OH!
AHHHHH
OW!
OW, OW, OW!
CHANGE?
GOT CHANGE?
我操!
NO, NO, DAMMIT
我受够了
THAT'S IT
都注意了 各位
THAT'S IT, EVERYONE
我们的薯片吃完了...
WE'RE OUT OF POP TARTS
你是在开玩笑吧?
NO, WE CAN'T BE
面对现实吧 我们要开始捱饿了
FACE IT, WE'RE GOING TO STARVE
不 别担心 这里还有一包呢
NO, WAIT THERE IS THERE IS STILL A BOX OVER HERE
哪些是草莓饼干 最恶心了!
THOSE ARE CHERRY, ICK!
等等 我有信号拉
WAIT, I HAVE GOT A SIGNAL
什么 真的吗?
WHAT? YOU DO?
快打电话给消防局啊
CALL THE FIRE DEPARTMENT
还是先打给我老婆吧
I'M CALLING MY WIFE
Mary Mary 宝贝 你没事吧?
MARY, MARY, BABY ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
噢 我们在这还挺好的
OH, MAYBE WE ARE GOING TO BE OKAY
问问她外面的情况
ASK HER WHAT IS HAPPENING
镇上有采取什么措施吗?
WHAT IS GOING ON OUT THERE
为什么没有救援人员过来啊?
NOBODY IS COMING FOR US
什么?
THEY WHAT?
不要呀!
NO!
这怎么可能呢!
THAT IS IMPOSSIBLE!
可是这怎么会.. 我们还没... 哈罗?
BUT HOW CAN THAT BE WE DIDN'T EVEN -- HELLO?
哈罗? Mary! Mary!
HELLO? MARY! MARY!
发生什么事了 Glen?
WHAT HAPPENED, GLEN?
镇上还是没有采取任何措施
THERE IS NO HELP COMING
她说由于那些流浪汉的缘故
SHE SAID BECAUSE OF ALL THE HOMELESS--
由于那些流浪汉的缘故 整个南方公园镇的物价狂跌
BECAUSE OF ALL THE HOMELESS IN SOUTH PARK PROPERTY VALUES PLUMMETED
银行冻结了以前我拿房子抵押的不动产...
I HAD TWO LIENS AGAINST THE HOUSE AND SO THE BANK IS FORECLOSING
我现在无家可归了...
I DON'T HAVE A HOME ANY MORE
Randy 你干什么呀?
RANDY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
他现在可是个流浪汉了
HE'S HOMELESS NOW
我们还是提防着点好..
WE AREN'T SAFE
我还那些流浪汉不一样啊
I'M NOT LIKE THEM
谁知道啊
NOT YET
可能过段时间你就会进化成他们那样了
IT IS ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
那你到底打算怎么做呢?
AND WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO, HUH?
把它的头打爆就好了吧
JUST BLOW HIS HEAD OFF
电视上有教过呢
IF WE HAVE TO
蹲下来 Glen
SIT DOWN, GLEN
Randy 你可不能这么...
RANDY, YOU CAN'T JUST--
蹲下!
SIT DOWN!
CHANGE
这也太扯了吧?
THIS IS CRAZY
他们怎么可以就这样把我的房子封掉呢?
HOW CAN THEY JUST TAKE AWAY MY HOUSE
我的财产全部都没有了 我现在一贫如洗了...
WHERE AM I SUPPOSED TO PUT ALL MY THINGS I DON'T HAVE FOR MY STUFF
我现在一贫如洗了...
WHERE AM I SUPPOSED TO PUT ALL MY STUFF
我得找个地方安定下来
I NEED TO PAY FOR STORAGE
如果我能凑些钱的话 也许还能勉强维持下去吧..
CAN I BORROW SOME MONEY TO PUT MY STUFF IN STORAGE
各位 可不可以帮帮我
COME ON, GUYS IF YOU HELP ME A LITTLE BIT
只要给我点零钱就好了嘛
???JUST A LITTLE CHANGE?
零钱...
CHANGE
这地方他妈怎么像被操过一样?
WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED HERE?
不要再前进了!
THAT'S FAR ENOUGH
快点擦干净你们的小屁股 滚出我们的常青树镇!
JUST MARCH YOUR BUTTS RIGHT BACK OUT OF OUR TOWN
我们只不过是请来请教一个问题
WE JUST CAME TO ASK A QUESTION
你们是流浪汉吗?
YOU HOMELESS OR HOMEOWNERS?
我们才九岁呢!
WE'RE NINE
噢 那意思说你们是少年流浪汉咯?
YEAH, WELL THAT MAKES YOU HOMELESS
快滚 不然我就要开枪了!
SO GET OUT OF HERE BEFORE YOU DIE
可是 我们只不过是来请教一下 如何解决流浪汉施虐的问题
LOOK, WE JUST NEED HELP WITH OUR OWN HOMELESS PROBLEM
没错 全部都是这个犹太人惹的祸
YEAH, THIS JEW HERE MADE THEM TAKE OVER OUR TOWN
闭嘴 Cartman!
SHUT UP, CARTMAN!
Cartman..
CARTMAN
Eric Cartman?
ERIC CARTMAN?
那个曾经只凭一个滑板 孤身飞越过30个流浪汉的街头传奇少年?
THE KID WHO JUMPED 30 HOMELESS PEOPLE ON A SKATEBOARD?
你们也知道这件事?
YOU HEARD ABOUT THAT?
那当然了
HEARD ABOUT IT
传说中如果你发挥实力的话 50个流浪汉对你而言也不过是小菜一碟
THEY SAID YOU HAVE HAVE EASILY CLEARED 50 HOMELESS WITH THAT JUMP
30个已经是我的极限了
30 WAS HARD ENOUGH
我操
OH, GOD
什么鸟30个流浪汉呀!
IT WASN'T 30!
不过一个罢了
IT WAS ONE
他只不过跨着他的傻逼小滑板 跳过一个流浪汉而已
HE JUMPED OVER ONE HOMELESS PERSON WITH HIS STUPID SKATEBOARD
而且就算那一次他也完成的非常勉强
AND HE BARELY MADE IT OVER THAT GUY
Kyle 别计较这些细节了
KYLE, KNOCK IT OFF
我们是来讨论如何解决流浪汉肆虐问题的
WE ARE HERE TO GET RID OF THE HOMELESS
而不是来辩论Cartman可以飞过几个流浪汉!
NOT HOW MANY HOMELESS CARTMAN CAN JUMP
求求你们了 快点告诉我们 你们是如何做到的吧
PLEASE, WE WANT YOU TO TELL US HOW YOU GOT RID OF THE HOMELESS IN YOUR TOWN
嗯 其实蛮简单的嘛
WELL, THAT WAS EASY
那些流浪汉大约是在 三个月前抵达我们常青树镇的
THE HOMELESS FIRST STARTED ARRIVING IN EVERGREEN ABOUT THREE MONTHS AGO
一开始不过就几个而已 要点零钱啊 在公园睡觉啊什么的
AT FIRST, THERE WERE ONLY A FEW OF THEM ASKING FOR CHANGE SLEEPING IN THE PARKS
可是它们的数量开始急剧增加
BUT THEN MORE SHOWED UP
接着我们忽然意识到一些不对劲的地方
AND WE REALIZED THERE WAS SOMETHING DIFFERENT ABOUT THEM
它们不断地积蓄着我们的零钱 直到它们可以..
THEY FED OFF OF OUR CHANGE TO THE POINT THAT THEY COULD
租下我们的住房...
ACTUALLY START RENTING APARTMENTS
可以想象不久之后 它们就可以买下我们的住房了
WE KNEW IT WOULDN'T BE LONG BEFORE THE HOMELESS ACTUALLY STARTED BUYING HOMES
到那时候 我们就分不清到底谁是流浪汉了..
AND THEN WE WOULD HAVE NO IDEA WHO WAS HOMELESS AND WHO WASN'T
也许你隔壁家的邻居就是个流浪汉
PEOPLE LIVING IN THE HOUSE RIGHT NEXT DOOR TO YOU COULD BE
可是你根本就无法知道真相
HOMELESS AND YOU WOULDN'T EVEN KNOW
人们之间的信用关系急剧下降
NOBODY COULD TRUST ANYBODY
于是全镇开始爆发了大规模械斗及战争
FIGHTS BROKE OUT AND WAR
就是那时我开始怀疑我的妻子
THAT IS WHEN I STARTED SUSPECTING THAT MY OWN WIFE
曾经与我相糑以沫20年的妻子 是一个流浪汉...
WHO I HAD BEEN LIVING WITH FOR 20 YEARS WAS ACTUALLY HOMELESS
我别无选择 只得在她睡着的时候偷偷把房子给点燃了
SO I HAD TO BURN HER IN HER BED WHILE SHE SLEPT
在她死掉之后 我发誓 一定不能让流浪汉毁掉我们镇
AFTER SHE DIED I VOWED I WOULDN'T LET THE HOMELESS DESTROY OUR TOWN
所以我们一起团结起来想出了 一个可以永久解决流浪汉问题的办法
SO WE CAME UP WITH A PLAN TO GET RID OF THEM ONCE AND FOR ALL
你这个臭婊子养的
YOU SON OF BITCH
你们根本就没有解决你们的流浪汉问题
YOU DIDN'T SOLVE YOUR HOMELESS PROBLEM
你们只不过把你们的流浪汉 全部都哄去了南方公园镇罢了
YOU JUST SENT ALL YOUR HOMELESS TO SOUTH PARK
就是这样 哈哈
THAT'S RIGHT, YES
- 什么? - 我就知道
- WHAT? - I KNEW IT
这根本就和我给的那20美元没有关系
IT WASN'T BECAUSE I GAVE THAT GUY $20
那些流浪汉都是从这儿来的!
THE HOMELESS ALL CAME FROM HERE
都是那些得克萨斯臭婊子的错!
AND TEXAS SENT THEM TO US
都是圣安东尼奥的那些贱人 把他们的问题转移到我们这儿的
THE PEOPLE IN SAN ANTONIO GOT RID OF THEIR HOMELESS
他们不停的宣传 说常青树镇是个多么多么好的地方
BY TELLING THEM WHAT A GREAT PLACE EVERGREEN WAS
可是你们根本就没有解决问题 你们不过是把问题转移给别人而已
BUT YOU DIDN'T SOLVE THE PROBLEM YOU JUST MOVED IT
这又怎么样呢 我们能活下来已经是万幸了
RIGHT, BUT WE SURVIVED
Tennis!
TENNIS!
Kristine?
KRISTINE?
你这个臭傻...
YOU SON OF A--
你他妈...
YOU ???
我没办法呀 Kristine 谁叫你是流浪汉呢?
I HAD TO, KRISTINE YOU WERE HOMELESS
我才不是流浪汉呢 你这个贱人?
NO, I WASN'T HOMELESS YOU ASSHOLE???
Kristine 我听不清楚你在说什么
KRISTINE, I CAN'T UNDERSTAND YOU
你把我的嘴唇烧掉了
BECAUSE YOU BURNED MY LIPS OFF
你说我把你的阴唇怎么了?
I URNED YOUR RIPS OFF?
我说的是"你把我嘴唇烧掉了.."
NO, YOU BURNED MY LIPS OFF
我实在是不懂你在说什么...
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT YOU ARE SAYING
OW!
OH.
伙计们 我们的家长就和这帮傻逼一样蠢
DUDE, OUR PARENTS ARE JUST AS STUPID AS THESE PEOPLE
我们的镇也会像这个镇一样完蛋的..
OUR TOWN IS GOING TO END UP JUST LIKE THIS
不 才不会呢 听好了哦 我可有个办法
NO, IT ISN'T COME ON, I HAVE AN IDEA
不 我们不能让Cartman再飞跃流浪汉了 这实在太危险了 Kyle
NO, WE ARE NOT HAVING CARTMAN JUMP ANY MORE HOMELESS PEOPLE, KYLE
那有不是我的主意..
THAT ISN'T MY IDEA
我刚才在那边的车间里面看到一部公车
I SAW A BUS IN THE GARAGE A COUPLE MILES BACK
我们可以把它改造一下
WE NEED TO MODIFY IT
我们到底要怎么做呀?
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
我们必须要干在我们的父母自相残杀之前 把这个问题给解决了
WE GONNA SAVE OUR PARENTS BEFORE THEY ALL KILL EACH OTHER
一部公车!
A BUS!
有一部公车开过来呢!
A BUS IS COMING!
是那些孩子们!
IT'S THE BOYS
他们改装了一辆公车来拯救我们...
THEY MODIFIED A BUS TO GET US OUT OF HERE
我就知道他们不会放弃我们的
I KNEW THEY WOULD COME BACK FOR US
太棒了!
ALL RIGHT!
看啊 Glen 我们得救了!
LOOK, GLEN, WE'RE SAFE!
我要调转方向了哦
I'M TURNING AROUND
他们为什么要掉头呀?
WHY ARE THEY TURNING
他们在干什么呀?
WHAT ARE THEY DOING?
不要离开我们...
DON'T LEAVE US
好啦 开震!
ALL RIGHT HIT IT!
愿耶稣保佑我们...
LET'S HOPE TO CHRIST THIS WORKS
* 加利福尼亚之爱 *
* CALIFORNIA LOVE *
* 加利福尼亚 流浪汉的温馨天堂 *
* CALIFORNIA, IS NICE TO THE HOMELESS *
* 加利福尼亚 流浪汉的和谐社会 *
* CALIFORNIA, THEY ARE NICE TO THE HOMELESS *
* 就在那圣塔莫尼克之城 *
* IN THE CITY, OF SANTA MONICA *
* 富人脑满肠肥 漫山遍野 *
* LOTS OF RICH PEOPLE *
* 流浪汉无需再为零钱发愁 *
* GIVING CHANGE TO THE HOMELESS *
CHANGE?
* 就在那布伦特伍德之城 *
* IN THE CITY, CITY OF ??? *
* 人们对流浪汉关怀备至 温习体贴 *
* THEY TAKE REALLY GOOD CARE OF ALL THE HOMELESS *
他们有在听耶 快开车!
THEY'RE LISTENING LET'S GO
* 就在那玛丽安娜得雷之城 *
* IN THE CITY OF MARINA DEL RAY??? *
* 他们与流浪汉打成一片 快乐无边 *
* THEY ARE SO NICE TO THE HOMELESS *
* 还建了庇护所 *
* ??? *
他们正在把流浪汉引走!
THEY'RE LEADING THEM AWAY
我们很快就能得救了
WE'RE GOING TO BE ALL RIGHT
噢 Glen 我们坚持下来了!
OH, GLEN WE MADE IT
* 加利福尼亚 *
* CALIFORNIA *
* 对流浪汉实在是超赞 *
* IS SO GOOD TO THE HOMELESS *
CHANGE?
* 加利福尼亚就是流浪汉的天堂 *
* CALIFORNIA IS KNOWN FOR THE HOMELESS *
* 就在那圣塔莫尼克之城 *
* IN THE CITY, CITY OF SANTA MONICA *
* MATT的别墅旁边 *
* RIGHT BY MATT'S HOUSE *
* 只要你是流浪汉 就能得到特别款待 *
* YOU CAN CHILL IF YOU'RE HOMELESS *
AGHAA...
YEAH
这回可是三个流浪汉!
THAT'S THREE HOMELESS!
我实在太屌了!
SUCK ON IT!
YA!
说实话 我真不明白你一开始想这个点子干嘛 Kyle
HONESTLY, I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU SEE IN THIS, KYLE
welcome to www.1000fr.com
双语合成 Lv&daisy